 var questions = [{
 	"question": "The first mechanical computer designed by charles babbage was called ?",
 	"option1": "abacus",
 	"option2": "analytical engine",
 	"option3": "calculator",
 	"option4": "ball",
 	"answer":"2"

}, {
	"question": "How to install react app?",
 	"option1": "$ npm install -g cordova ",
 	"option2": "$ npm install -j create-project-app",
 	"option3": "$ npm install -g create-react-app",
 	"option4": "$ npm install -g create-app-react",
 	"answer":"3"
}, {
	"question": "How to create react-app?",
	"option1": "$ create-react-app my-app-name",
	"option2": "$ create-cordova-app my-app-name",
	"option3": "$ create-apache-npm my-app name",
	"option4": "$create-react-app",
	"answer": "1"

}, {
	"question": "who invented c?",
	"option1": "dennis",
	"option2": "Dennis Ritchie",
	"option3": "denistro ritchies",
	"option4": "google chrome",
	"answer": "2"

}, {
	"question": "In what year was Google launched on the web?",
	"option1": "1997",
	"option2": "2017",
	"option3": "1999",
	"option4": "1998",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "In computing what is Ram short for?",
	"option1": "Random Access Memory",
	"option2": "Random Acadimics Memory",
	"option3": "Random Access Member",
	"option4": "Random Accounting Memory",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "Which unit is an indication for the sound quality of MP3?",
	"option1": "mmppbbss",
	"option2": "ps",
	"option3": "mbps",
	"option4": "Kbps",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "What is the name of the network of computers from which the Internet has emerged?",
	"option1": "Arpanetshaker",
	"option2": "Arplanet",
	"option3": "Arpanet",
	"option4": "Arpanetas",
	"answer": "3"
}, {
	"question": "What is the country top-level domain of Belgium?",
	"option1": "who .is domain",
	"option2": "The .be domain",
	"option3": "The .be a domainating",
	"option4": "domain only",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "How many oscars did the Titanic movie got?",
	"option1": "12",
	"option2": "13",
	"option3": "14",
	"option4": "11",
	"answer": "4"
}];


